Reginald Capagcuan

Lodi, NJ 07644 973-594-6713 | rejjee@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/reginald-capagcuan-88a245127

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I specialize in front- and back-end web development using Knockout.js and .Net framework, respectively. In the last three years, I worked at software development companies developing web applications for global enterprises. I have proven ability to work with new technology and accomplish tasks with varying complexity.

SKILLS

Full-stack web development experience using Microsoft .Net and Knockout.js

- Web API, ASP.NET MVC, .Net Framework, C#
- CSS, HTML, Bootstrap, SASS, PrePros
- Knockout.js, JavaScript, JSON, Ajax
- SQL Server, T-SQL
- Visual Studio, Team Foundation Server, Git

EXPERIENCE

Application Developer

Sharphat, Inc. - Englewood Cliffs, NJ October 2017 - September 2019

Sharphat, Inc. is a custom software development company. Developed web applications for clients such as the National Football League and Canadian Football League. Used Web API, MVC, T-Sql, Knockout.js, .NET libraries Dapper and NLog, etc. Examples of work accomplished were:

- Modernizing a legacy Web Forms/VB application into a single-page application using Web API/C#/Knockout.js
- Full life cycle development of the Player Health Safety project for the NFL using .Net Web API, Knockout.js, SQL
- Displaying real-time game statistics using XML, SignalR and Knockout.js
- Developing address-resolution features using Google Places API
- Automating the creation of server images and instances and starting new servers by developing an API client for AWS Amazon EC2
- Facilitating analysis of employee productivity by developing a graphical, interactive tool using Atlassian JIRA dashboards, SQL and the Highcharts JavaScript library

Application Developer

Decusoft - Ramsey, NJ January 2017 - August 2017

Worked as part of a team on a commercial HR web application for compensation management. Developed with Microsoft .Net stack and Knockout.js. Examples of work were:

- Migrating application from Web Forms to Web API and Knockout.js
- Displaying real-time charts on the front-end with drill-down and filtering functions using the Highcharts JavaScript library.
- Generating an Excel spreadsheet with real-time compensation data based on the user's data authorization using Infragistics JavaScript library.

Used Sammy.js, AmplifyJS, Coffeescript, SourceGear Vault, Jenkins Continuous Integration, etc.

Application Developer

LanguageWorks, a division of Ubiqus - New York, NY February 2006 - May 2016

Progressively transitioned from a Lotus Notes developer role into .Net development over several years, working on full life-cycle development of several applications. Examples of work include:

- Client Zone, a Web Forms application that allowed clients to enter job orders and interfaced with legacy Lotus Notes applications.
- Developing a billing web application for third-party vendors.
- Modernizing the LanguageWorks company website.
- Middleware tools that saved man-hours by automatically converting raw files to Excel.
- Programs that migrated data from Lotus Notes to 4D platform.
- Developing Visual Studio Tools for Office (VSTO) plugin for Outlook.
- Providing desktop and server support to local and international employees and partners.

Used C#, MVC 4, Web API 2, Entity Framework 5, SQL Server 2008, jQuery, JavaScript, CSS, Ajax, JSON, WCF/web services, Web Forms, Subversion for version control, Visual Studio Tools for Office, Microsoft Outlook, Nunit for unit testing

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science, Information Technology
De La Salle University - Manila, Philippines

WORK AUTHORIZATION

Authorized to work in the U.S. without sponsorship